<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ayushe.com</title>
    <link>https://ayushenagpal.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Ayushe.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <managingEditor>ayushenagpal@gmail.com (Ayushe Nagpal)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>ayushenagpal@gmail.com (Ayushe Nagpal)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ayushenagpal.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Glorification of Western Culture</title>
      <link>https://ayushenagpal.github.io/blog/2020-06-17-wake-up-call/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>ayushenagpal@gmail.com (Ayushe Nagpal)</author>
      <guid>https://ayushenagpal.github.io/blog/2020-06-17-wake-up-call/</guid>
      <description>For every George Floyd and Breonna Taylor, there is a Sonu Sah and a Lal Swami and a Naresh Shinde and a Sukhdev Singh that go unnoticed in their own country that is heavily advocating for injustices in the west.
As I swipe through my Instagram stories, the advocacy for the Black Lives Movement and the death of George Floyd makes me feel gratified - people are using their social media to wake up and inform and educate others over the injustices black people face.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mental Health Matters</title>
      <link>https://ayushenagpal.github.io/blog/2020-06-26-mental-health-matters/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>ayushenagpal@gmail.com (Ayushe Nagpal)</author>
      <guid>https://ayushenagpal.github.io/blog/2020-06-26-mental-health-matters/</guid>
      <description>In the wake of the loss of a Bollywood and TV show actor, Sushant Singh Rajput, I have seen a surge in the number of people advocating for mental health by sharing resources on social media. While it is important to share those resources on social media for people that are affected by a mental health disorder to reach out to, we don’t realize that it is more important for our society to create a safe space for people to open up about their feelings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Time for Change</title>
      <link>https://ayushenagpal.github.io/blog/2020-06-02-a-time-for-change/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>ayushenagpal@gmail.com (Ayushe Nagpal)</author>
      <guid>https://ayushenagpal.github.io/blog/2020-06-02-a-time-for-change/</guid>
      <description>As the 5th day of civil riots over the death of George Floyd approaches and the &amp;ldquo;trend&amp;rdquo; of the black lives matter movement on social media grows and society establishes it’s time for this movement after the collapse of politics and governance leaves no other option, I’ve come to reflect on and realize a few things.
Racism in this country is far more deep rooted than most people think. From 269 years of slavery to 99 years of Jim Crow Laws to 86 years of Lynching to 14 years of Civil Rights fight to a lack of respect from others and police brutality to date.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Selfless and The Selfish</title>
      <link>https://ayushenagpal.github.io/blog/2020-04-13-the-selfless/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>ayushenagpal@gmail.com (Ayushe Nagpal)</author>
      <guid>https://ayushenagpal.github.io/blog/2020-04-13-the-selfless/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://ayushenagpal.github.io/images/selfless.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A crisis brings out the best and worst in people. Throughout this situation we have seen people self-sacrificing on the front lines and we have seen people ignorantly exposing themselves in the name of demanding their rights. One echoes of bravery and humanity at its best. The other is conceited and foolish.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Just the Beginning</title>
      <link>https://ayushenagpal.github.io/blog/2020-03-15-just-the-beginning/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>ayushenagpal@gmail.com (Ayushe Nagpal)</author>
      <guid>https://ayushenagpal.github.io/blog/2020-03-15-just-the-beginning/</guid>
      <description>One month ago, the corona virus was something that was happening somewhere else. It came to us sooner than we expected and stronger than we expected. While we worked on our work in class, my teacher put the live stream of the governor up in class as speculations of school being closed for the school year traveled fast.
And of course, my class watched the governor intently with a common hope to hear that schools would be closed in an effort to slow down the corona virus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Stress of Final Exams</title>
      <link>https://ayushenagpal.github.io/blog/2019-12-19-stress-of-final-exams/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>ayushenagpal@gmail.com (Ayushe Nagpal)</author>
      <guid>https://ayushenagpal.github.io/blog/2019-12-19-stress-of-final-exams/</guid>
      <description>Moving from across the world, my expectations for an American high school were&amp;hellip; well - High School Musical. Lots of singing and dancing. A star athlete falling in love with a nerdy me. My Troy Bolton sweeping me off my feet. Students huddled in cliques worrying about the dress they’re wearing to prom 5 months early and gossiping about who the Prom Queen will be. However, my expectations did not live up to reality, as they don’t in most cases.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How This Time of the Year Imapcts Me</title>
      <link>https://ayushenagpal.github.io/blog/2019-11-21-how-this-time-of-the-year-impacts-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>ayushenagpal@gmail.com (Ayushe Nagpal)</author>
      <guid>https://ayushenagpal.github.io/blog/2019-11-21-how-this-time-of-the-year-impacts-me/</guid>
      <description>They say Christmas is the most wonderful time of the year. Personally, mine would be waking up before my alarm to realize I still have 2 hours to sleep left. But that’s just my opinion. While my family’s constant playing of Christmas music in the car slowly drives me insane, my increased tolerance after traveling during the holidays certainly reflects a way this time of the year impacts me in small ways.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Detrimental Drugs</title>
      <link>https://ayushenagpal.github.io/blog/2019-10-3-detrimental-drugs/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>ayushenagpal@gmail.com (Ayushe Nagpal)</author>
      <guid>https://ayushenagpal.github.io/blog/2019-10-3-detrimental-drugs/</guid>
      <description>The way mental health is treated in our healthcare system is broken. I remember, after an emergency visit to the hospital, my brother returned home calmer than his usual cheerful self. Barely talking, barely interacting, barely moving. Simply returning a long stare to our efforts to talk to him. Earlier that day, he had had a complex panic attack and was rushed to the hospital, where nurses injected drugs to control the attack, not to make him better but to simply to quiet him down.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Drive Behind My (Hopefully) Future Career</title>
      <link>https://ayushenagpal.github.io/blog/2019-9-4-the-drive-behind-my-hopefully-future-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>ayushenagpal@gmail.com (Ayushe Nagpal)</author>
      <guid>https://ayushenagpal.github.io/blog/2019-9-4-the-drive-behind-my-hopefully-future-/</guid>
      <description>Hi readers! I&amp;rsquo;m a junior in high school and I was inspired to take an interest in the topic of medicine and neuroscience because growing up with a brother with special needs, I’ve noticed how people interact with him, and others like him, as well as wondered how the brain’s activity affects his actions. As the younger sibling, I&amp;rsquo;ve heard about the several brain surgeries he&amp;rsquo;s had after he suffered from hydrocephalus (fluid retention in the brain), which instilled a desire in me to learn more about the brain&amp;rsquo;s conditions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Art</title>
      <link>https://ayushenagpal.github.io/page/art/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>ayushenagpal@gmail.com (Ayushe Nagpal)</author>
      <guid>https://ayushenagpal.github.io/page/art/</guid>
      <description>Since a young age, art has been a way to express myself and something I resorted to to take a break away from my world. I&amp;rsquo;ve always been passionate about it, my favorite medium being acrylic painting. I hope to continue creating art as a hobby!  April 19th 2020 - Too Many Locks, Not Enough Keys
 April 6th 2020 - In a World of Darkness
 April 3rd 2020 - Untethered</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CS Projects</title>
      <link>https://ayushenagpal.github.io/page/csprojects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>ayushenagpal@gmail.com (Ayushe Nagpal)</author>
      <guid>https://ayushenagpal.github.io/page/csprojects/</guid>
      <description>Internships  Procter &amp;amp; Gamble - Olay Super Bowl LIV Intern January - February 2020 I had the incredible opportunity to be one of 7 out of 185,000 Girls Who Code members and work with Olay&amp;rsquo;s team to build landing pages as a part of their Super Bowl LIV Campaign, #MakeSpaceForWomen. Olay partnered with Girls Who Code in a mission to close the gender gap and change the image of a &amp;ldquo;programmer&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Media</title>
      <link>https://ayushenagpal.github.io/page/media/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>ayushenagpal@gmail.com (Ayushe Nagpal)</author>
      <guid>https://ayushenagpal.github.io/page/media/</guid>
      <description>My Radio Interview
COVID-19 Video
Speech &amp;amp; Debate States Tournament Wooster Vlog in Spanish</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Misc Projects</title>
      <link>https://ayushenagpal.github.io/page/misc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>ayushenagpal@gmail.com (Ayushe Nagpal)</author>
      <guid>https://ayushenagpal.github.io/page/misc/</guid>
      <description>SASR - Mentor &amp;amp; Tutor Program Founder
2012 - Present My work with SASR started when I was a mere 9 years old. Tagging along with my mom, I&amp;rsquo;d spend hours after school working with students with special needs as a mentor and a friend. During that time I co-organized a picnic for students that attended the SASR center and underprivileged children in India. Since then, I&amp;rsquo;ve continued my work with them even after moving across the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://ayushenagpal.github.io/page/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>ayushenagpal@gmail.com (Ayushe Nagpal)</author>
      <guid>https://ayushenagpal.github.io/page/projects/</guid>
      <description>CS Projects Other Pojects </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
